

MOHAMED LAARBI RAMOUZ

Software Developer

- Manara 24,15
 Morocco, Tangier, 90000
- **•** 01.12.1994
- +212 6 75 91 15 97 med.t3ch07@gmail.com

SOFTWARE SKILLS

PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS



C, C#, C++, JavaScript



Python, Java, Ruby



MultiMedia



LANGUAGES

English

German C

B1

French C

Spanish

B1

PROFILE

Hard-working programmer with 5+ years experience developing, testing, and maintaining enterprise software applications, and with a flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time.

Designed and developed dozens of advanced applications from use cases and functional requirements.

EDUCATION

01.2017 - 03.2018

Deutsch institut, Tangier

Goethe Deutsch Zertifikat B1

2013 - 2015

OFPPT-ISMONTIC, Tangier

Multimedia Development (vocational training)

2013

Anoual High School, Tangier

Baccalaureate, Physics

EXPERIENCE

08.2015 - present

System Base, IT Department

-Software Developer

- Built up to 5 applications projects per month for more than 5 years,
- using: PHP, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, Json, HTML, CSS, C#, C++, Java, Bash, MySQL,
- Familiar with Symfony, Zend, Angular, Xshell, WordPress, Git,
- Built Android applications. (Android Studio)
- Worked with multiple systems, Windows, Linux, Ubuntu.
- Provided Technical support.

04.2015 - 05.2015

Amendis

-Trainee

Collaborated with multiple teams daily to build full stack applications for clients.

2015

School Project

Designed and developed a 3D video game.

SKILLS

- Communicative
- Creativity
- Organized
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Punctuality
- Decision Making
- Adaptability
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork